

Swann Htet Aung

BoAungKyaw Street, Ywar Gout Myo Thit Quarter, Pyinmana | PH: 09754308079 | swannhtetaung.ss@gmail.com

PERSONNAL INFORMATION

Full Name Swann Htet Aung

Date of Birth 15 June 1994

Nationality Myanmar

Race/Religion Burma, Buddhist

Marital Status Single

Language Myanmar, English, Japanese (N5-attending)

JOB Description

Experience in various areas of Information Technology especially Java & PHP Application Development. I also have knowledge and experience in mobile application development and involved as a Team Lead in development of mobile application project during Internship Program. And I experience in Software Installation, training and service to the end users, Plus Finance Sector and Government Relations.

EDUCATION / CERTIFICATION

Dec 2010 – Sep 2017 Bachelor of Computer Science B.C.Sc.

Computer University, Mandalay, Myanmar

Jan 2020 Professional Advanced Excel Training

Myanmar Excel Expert Team

Oct 2020 Understanding Capital Markets

Strategy First University

WORK EXPERIENCE

1. Software Developer

2017 – 2018

Mandalay Region Computer Professionals Association + Mandalay Region Computer Industry Association , At Myanmar Information Institute Technology(MIIT)

- Task includes testing, validation, installation and configuration.
- Design web pages and create web application prototypes.
- Database Designing and Data Collecting
- Documentation, Presentation and Management
- Backend with PHP
- Hybrid Mobile Application with Ionic Framework

WORK EXPERIENCE

2. Software Service Technician

2018 - 2020

Galaxy Software Company (iStock, CafePOS, HotelPro, SchoolMS)

- Training to the users (CEO, Manager, Accountant, Cashier, Chef, Waiter and so on)
- Servicing and fixing to the user errors with phone, AnyDesk, Teamviewer and go to the sites when they needed
- Report customer feedback to the QR Team weekly and monthly
- If necessary, Marketing around the NayPyiTaw Region

Technical Skills

- System Analysis & Design, Solutions, UML
- Web Design
- Development Language:
 - PHP (Laravel / Codelgniter Framework), Java
 - Vue.js,React, jQuery, JavaScript, Ajax, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap
 - Ionic 3, Flutter, REST api, Laravel api
- Database Server:
 - Apache/2.4.47, SQLite, MSSQL

Soft Skills

- Good manner, Personality, Time Management
- Self-Confident, Self-Study
- Teamwork, Leadership, Problem Solving
- Concentration, Work ethic, Positive-Thinking, Customer Sevice and etc.,

AVAILABILITY

Ready to start

My Portfolio and simple project links

- https://swannhtetaung.me/
- https://omnifood.swannhtetaung.me/
- https://bootstrap.swannhtetaung.me/
- https://shopules.swannhtetaung.me/
- https://cinematicketbooking.swannhtetaung.me/
- https://laraveleshop.swannhtetaung.me/
- https://expenselist.swannhtetaung.me/

- → My Portfolio
- → Design Project
- → Bootstrap Project
- → E-commerce Project with Pure PHP
- → Cinema Ticket Booking Project with Laravel
- → E-commerce Project with Laravel
- → React Project